ARYA AGNI PRADANA FIRDAUS

081368899879 | Bekasi, Jawa Barat. | 17836

<u>aryaagnipradana@gmail.com</u> | <u>linkedin.com/in/aryaagnipradana</u> | <u>https://portfolio-aryaagnipradana.netlify.app/</u>

Junior Web Developer | Front-End Developer | Software Developer | Website Developer

SUMMARY

Logical and results-driven Web Developer dedicated to programming and optimizing user-focused websites for customers with various business objectives. Experienced working with teams, especially Front-End Developers. Possesses solid knowledge in HTML5/CSS3, Javascript (ES6), NodeJS, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap, and ReactJS.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITAS JAMBI Jambi

Bachelor in Agribusiness | GPA: 3.49 / 4

2019 - 2023

Thesis title "Analisis Kelayakan Bisnis Minuman Berdasarkan Indikator Finansial (Studi Kasus Pada Cafe Kati Coffee di Kecamatan Cikarang Utara Kabupaten Bekasi)". Analyze business income and conduct cash flow analysis to determine whether the business is feasible with indicators of NPV, IRR, B/C Ratio, Profitability Ratio and Payback Period.

EXPERIENCE

PT. DICODING AKADEMI INDONESIA

Bandung (Online)

Front-End Developer, Internship

August 2022 - January 2023

- Lead and managed a team of 4 developers in a Capstone Project, creating a recipe catalog website and discussion forum 'Buku Resepku'
- Developed front-end architecture by paying attention to excellent features such as Object Oriented Program (OOP), Progressive Web Apps (PWAs) and Mobile First Approach.
- Employed Fetch(Native) and JSON technologies to create a seamless data exchange between the front-end and back-end and implemented it in CRUD feature.

FACULTY OF AGRICULTURE, UNIVERSITAS JAMBI

Mendalo Darat, Jambi

Secretarial Staff, Part Time

April 2022 - August 2022

- Responsible and handling the administration files that required by the faculty from around 120 seminar's participant such from google spreadsheet that automatically recorded from google form.
 Developing a WordPress website to be used as a platform for promotion, information dissemination, and registration for Seminar purposes
- Developing and implementing registration procedures via website, seminar payment procedures, Letter of Acceptance (LoA) delivery, and journal delivery
- Maximizing data collection by transferring data online via spreadsheets, enabling data entry tasks to be conducted online and monitored in real-time.

DIGITAL TALENT SCHOLARSHIP 2022

Jambi (Online)

IT Support, Scholarship

May 2022 – July 2022

- Implemented the basic to advanced terminal operations using programming language, basic of language C, the Secure Shell protocol using OpenSHH, Linux system administration and fundamentals of operation system such as file system, package manager and desktop environment by practicing in real environment.
- Implemented fundamentals to intermediate knowledge of Network. Such as protocols (TCP/IP, HTTP,

UDP/IP, FTP), application layer, IP addresses (IPv4 and IPv6) and Domain Name Systems in real work simulation.

CERTIFICATION

- IT Support, Digital Talent, Number: FGA/2022/2527/149252735101-2299, 2022
- Front-End Web dan Back-End Developer, PT Dicoding Akademi Indonesia, Number: DCD/SIB3/GRAD/XXII-12/F226X0448, 2022
- Test of English as a Foreign Language (Score 533), Universitas Jambi, Number: 03/UN.21.16/BS/2023, 2023

SKILL

- Hard Skills: Agribusiness, Finance and Accounting, Investment, Business Development, Business Feasibility Analysis, Investment, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript ECMAScript 2015 (ES6), Functional Programming, Promise, Mobile First Apporach, Accessibility, Progressive Web Apps (PWAs), NodeJS, Tailwindcss, Bootstrap, React, ReactJS, Web Performance, CI/CD Deployment
- **Soft Skills**: Hard Worker, Teamwork, Project Management, Time Management, Communication, Problem Solving, Detail Oriented
- **Software Skills**: Microsoft Word, Microsoft Power Point, Microsoft Excel, Google Workspace (Spreadsheet, Docs, Slide), Visual Studio Code, Postman, Linux OS
- Languages: Indonesia (Native), English (Intermediate, TOEFL 533)